{
    "subject": "resource/Gabriella_Wilde",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Wilde, Gabriella",
    "human_readable": "The name of Gabriella Wilde is Wilde, Gabriella.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9621566534042358,
            "question": "What is Gabriella Wilde's surname?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9595261216163635,
            "question": "Is 'Wilde' Gabriella Wilde's given name or surname?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9540064334869385,
            "question": "What is Gabriella Wilde's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9130727052688599,
            "question": "What is the order of Gabriella Wilde's names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8552681803703308,
            "question": "How would you write Gabriella Wilde's name in the format 'Last Name, First Name'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8495894074440002,
            "question": "What is the most common way to write Gabriella Wilde's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8274982571601868,
            "question": "If someone only knew Gabriella Wilde's first name, how could they find her full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7904205322265625,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a situation where knowing both parts of Gabriella Wilde's name would be important?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7817078828811646,
            "question": "How many parts make up Gabriella Wilde's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5908101201057434,
            "question": "If you met Gabriella Wilde, how would you address her formally?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Gabriella Wilde is Wilde, Gabriella.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4594_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many parts make up Gabriella Wilde's full name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4594_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give an example of a situation where knowing both parts of Gabriella Wilde's name would be important?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4594_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If someone only knew Gabriella Wilde's first name, how could they find her full name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4594_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4594_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4594_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4594_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4594_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4594_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4594_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4594_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4594_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4594_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4594_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response to your question:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Gabriella Wilde's full name, confirming that \"The name of Gabriella Wilde is Wilde, Gabriella\" is correct. Various forms of her name are mentioned, including Gabriella Zanna Vanessa Anstruther-Gough-Calthorpe and known professionally as Gabriella Wilde or Gabriella Calthorpe."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the name of Gabriella Wilde as stated in most of the provided context information is \"Gabriella Zanna Vanessa Anstruther-Gough-Calthorpe\", and only occasionally referred to as \"Wilde\" or \"Calthorpe\".",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}